Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nataliia-mykhailova-06b94522 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

AJAX

MySQL

Subversion

Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Ukrainian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Front-End JavaScript Frameworks: AngularJS

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools

Nataliia Mykhailova

Software developer at Quintiq

Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada

Summary

Programming languages/technologies: TypeScript, AngularJS, npm,

Highcharts, JavaScript, HTML/CSS/XML/Ajax; Java, JDBC, JSP/

Servlet, Ant, Maven; C++; PHP;

Delphi – no experience of commercial development;

Architecture: good knowledge of OOP;

CMS: Magento, Joomla;

Frameworks: ExtJS;Symfony;

RDBMS: Oracle, MySQL;

OS: Windows, Linux -user;

Version controls systems: CVS, SVN;

Grafics: Photoshop;

Experience

Quintiq, a Dassault Systèmes company

Software engineer

October 2012 - April 2018 (5 years 7 months)

's-Hertogenbosch

DIO

Java Developer

August 2011 - October 2012 (1 year 3 months)

National Bank of Ukraine

Java Developer

October 2010 - August 2011 (11 months)

web site development and support (Java, JSP/Servlet, JDBC,Oracle,Ant, JavaScript,XML,HTML/CSS)

Ltd. Siopt

Php Developer

October 2009 - June 2010 (9 months)

*web site development and support (PHP,Javascript,HTML,CSS,Symfony(1 project));

Page 1 of 2

*internet shops development and support (Magento);
Project examples: http://www.lauratheiss.com, http://
unesco.kolaborator.si/,http://sitedesigner.com.ua/demo4646/, http://
napodarki.com.ua/,http://spletnik.si/gomila,https://swbworld.com/,etc.

FCA

Freelance WEB Developer July 2009 - October 2009 (4 months)

*web site development (PHP,Javascript,HTML,CSS,Ajax)

Project examples: Ukraine Business (http://www.ukrainebusiness.com.ua)

Ltd. Commerce Lab

Php Developer

September 2008 - April 2009 (8 months)

*web site development and support (PHP,Javascript,HTML,CSS,Ajax);

- * code refactoring;
- * design and implementation of new services;
- * database design and implementation(MySQL);

Education

National Technical University of Ukraine 'Kyiv Polytechnic Institute' master, Computer science · (2004 - 2010)